https://www.tanninglotionlewies.com/privacy-policy.html

Email
PasswordForgot your password?
Blog
Get the color of the skin that you deserve by using tanning products on a daily basis. Best of all, you can buy all the brands at below retail prices. Feel proud when you look in the mirror and see a color that is both easy on the eye and satisfying. Shop now with huge savings only available on the internet.
All Products Heavily Discounted from Normal Retail Prices
Home Page/Privacy Policy
Shop by Brand
Shop by Brand
Tanning Lotions by Brand
New Tanning Products 2021
Tanning Lotions 2020
Australian Gold
Privacy Policy
Lewie’s Tanning, located at the web address http://www.lewiestanning.com, wants your experiences with us to be enjoyable, easy to understand and safe.
Our privacy policy ensures that you understand how and why we collect your data when you make a purchase or communicate with us via telephone or email.
You can review this policy at any time. We reserve the right to update this privacy policy at any time.
Do you collect my IP address or use cookies?
Lewie’s Tanning collects your IP address and stores cookies so our website will load faster and also to store information. We need this information so we can store your shopping cart.
We may also store this data in case we need this information when diagnosing server problems, and to collect basic demographic information (such as what country you’re from, etc.)
Do you need my personal or billing information?
When you start communication with us, register to save an online account or make a purchase, we’ll collect specific data about you that you input voluntarily. This includes your full name, email address, shipping address, and financial information (credit card numbers, etc).
We use your shipping address to send your order and it’s only stored if you choose to save this information when creating an online account. Your financial information is used once to bill you for the products you ordered. You can voluntarily save this information in your account for faster checkout in the future.
Do you send me emails? How can I opt out?
We use your email address to contact you about your order. Occasionally we may send you emails we think may interest you; for example news about company updates, or alerts about sale items or discounts. You may opt out at any time by clicking the link at the bottom of the email that says “Unsubscribe.”
How do you keep my information safe?
Lewie’s Tanning wants to keep your private information safe when using our website. Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard for the most secure commerce transactions. This technology encrypts your personal information so it can’t be accessed or collected by anyone else.
How can I pay for my items? Is it safe to give you my information?
Lewie’s Tanning accepts all major credit cards: Discover, Master Card, Visa and American Express. We also accept payment by money order or personal check. We use Itransact, using SSL, to process your information and we never release this information for any reason other than for your one-time order.
Who owns this website?
Tanning Enterprises is a limited liability company. (L.L.C.) We’re an independent distributor. We’re not associated with, affiliated with, nor do we represent, any manufacturer or distributor of any tanning products displayed on our websites. We use product names on our website for identification purposes only. All registered trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
Prices and product availability are subject to change at any time. We’re not responsible for online errors or typos.
2020 Tanning Enterprises.
